eshop30.com 2015-08-17

# Privacy Policy - Shopping Online Get Discounts on Products For India

Thank you for visiting my web site. This privacy policy tells you how I use personal information collected here. Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information. By using the site, you accept the practices described in this privacy policy.

### Amazon Associates Program

This website is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program. This means, in particular, that if you follow a link to amazon.com or any other national version of Amazon website and then make a purchase within 24 hours, I will receive a small percentage of what you pay to Amazon (but your price will stay exactly the same).

I, however, **never link to specific products just in order to advertize them**. I link only to the products that I genuinely find helpful (usually T Shirt I have made; it would be a shame if I didn’t find those helpful), and the webpages linking to such products express my honest opinion on the products. In other words, I never recommend a product just in order to persuade you to buy it; I recommend it because I myself find it useful.

### Collection of Information

I can collect personally identifiable information, like names, postal addresses, email addresses, etc., when voluntarily submitted by my visitors. This information is only used to fulfill your specific request, unless you give me permission to use it in another manner. I never share any information with third parties, unless required by the law.

### Cookies

To support your privacy, this website **doesn’t use any cookies**. Third party services used by the website, such as Disqus for comments and the Google+ button, may use their own cookies to fulfil your specific requests.

_I reserve the right to make changes to this policy._
